<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>UpTech</title>
        <link>https://www.uptech.cf/</link>
        <description>UpTech is a site dedicated to technology advice and lessons.We are interested in computer technology and all things linked to it.We will provide you with high-quality content on a wide range of themes and computer technology.</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 15:52:11 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://www.uptech.cf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>How to Install Tool-X in Termux</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/how-to-install-tool-x-in-termux/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 15:52:11 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/how-to-install-tool-x-in-termux/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/how-to-install-tool-x-in-termux/img/toolx.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Did you realize you can transform your smartphone into a true hacking machine? All of this can be accomplished with the assistance of Termux and Tool-X. If you already have termux installed on your phone, you may install all tools with a single click. If you do not have it, you can read how here What Is Termux How to Install It and First Steps After Instalation.
 What exactly is Tool-X?]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>What Are Yubikeys Used For?</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/what-are-yubikeys-used-for/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 17:09:35 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/what-are-yubikeys-used-for/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/what-are-yubikeys-used-for/img/yubico.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>What Exactly Are Yubikeys, And How Do You Use Them?  Yubico is a brand of security keys that provide physical two-factor authentication.
The YubiKey is a hardware two-factor authentication device. The YubiKey is intended to ensure that the owner of the device, not the device, is the one that logs into the account. Each key is unique and can be used to access your online accounts as well as secure sensitive data.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>What Are the Benefits of Linux?</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/what-are-the-benefits-of-linux/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 13:59:25 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/what-are-the-benefits-of-linux/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/what-are-the-benefits-of-linux/img/li.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>What Exactly is Linux? Linux is a UNIX-like operating system which is completely free, open source and community supported.
Linux is the most popular open source operating system that is the foundation of most of the Internet.
Linux powers most of the web.
Linux powers the servers that provide the infrastructure to the entire Internet.
Linux powers the mobile phones and tablets.
The linux operating system was created in 1991 by Linus Torvalds.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Install Metasploit in Termux?</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/how-to-install-metasploit-in-termux/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:12:14 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/how-to-install-metasploit-in-termux/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/how-to-install-metasploit-in-termux/img/metasploit.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>What Is Metasploit  Metasploit is a free, open-source penetration testing framework. It is designed for use against a single computer or network, in contrast to other penetration testing tools such as nikto and cain and abel that target a network of computers. This is done to reduce the time spent in scanning for a network, increasing the speed at which exploits can be found.
The metasploit framework contains pre-configured plugins and exploits, although the user can also write their own.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Why Facebook Changed Its Name to Meta?</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/why-facebook-changed-its-name-to-meta/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 06:38:42 &#43;0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/why-facebook-changed-its-name-to-meta/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/why-facebook-changed-name/img/fb.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>When Zuckerberg started Facebook in the dorms of Harvard, he was a computer science student who was very interested in social issues like privacy and social movements.
He and his friends used it to keep track of one another, but within a few years it became a tool of mass consumerism and media manipulation, and it attracted the attention of the political and media establishment.
The result is the social network we all know today, which now serves to create and distribute images of and about what people want to be.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Can Smartphones Get Viruses?</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/can-smartphones-get-viruses/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 23:59:17 &#43;0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/can-smartphones-get-viruses/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/can-smartphones-get-viruses/img/phone-security.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>With over 4.5 billion smartphones in use worldwide, smartphone users are increasingly vulnerable to malware and virus infections.
Smartphones can be infected by phishing emails, malicious websites, and malicious applications. Even a simple process such as downloading an app to your phone is fraught with security risks.
Smartphones are also vulnerable to the traditional internet threats of malware and viruses.
Approximately 80% of smartphone users access the internet via their smartphones.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>What Exactly Is A Mastodon, And Why Should You Give It A Shot?</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/what-is-mastodon-and-why-should-you-give-it-a-shot/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 23:59:02 &#43;0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/what-is-mastodon-and-why-should-you-give-it-a-shot/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/mastodon/img/mastodon.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>What is a Mastodon?  When most people think of social media, they think of Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, and other similar platforms. However, individuals are becoming increasingly conscious that they are data miners with a large percentage of censored content.
Is there another option, or do we have to completely leave social media? Fortunately, the answer is yes. Thanks to social media, we can connect with people online, and they should be open to us.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Everything You Need to Know About Windows 11</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/everything-you-need-to-know-about-windows-11/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 21:33:46 &#43;0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/everything-you-need-to-know-about-windows-11/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/windows-11/img/w6.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>When Microsoft released Windows 10 in 2015, he stated that it would be the final version of Windows. So, in essence, all new functionality will be gained through Windows updates. It was a headache, and many people disliked them for good reason. They destroy systems, delete data, and sometimes just appear at the wrong moment when you are in the middle of something. Microsoft eventually improved them, although there were still some issues.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>What Is Termux How to Install It and First Steps After Instalation</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/what-is-termux-how-to-install-it-and-first-steps-after-instalation/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:48:32 &#43;0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/what-is-termux-how-to-install-it-and-first-steps-after-instalation/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/what-is-termux/img/termux.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Introduction To Termux TERMUX is a terminal emulator for Android system. It means that you can access to the system on your phone through a terminal like on Linux, Windows or macOS. Since Android is built on Linux, Termux use Unix-like commands.
Unfortunately app is not available for iphone.
Those who use Linux and macOS will be familiar with commands.
For those who use Windows will be little unfamiliar since CMD ( Command Prompt ) use different commands.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to Play Music in Termux</title>
    <link>https://www.uptech.cf/how-to-play-music-in-termux/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:29:38 &#43;0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.uptech.cf/how-to-play-music-in-termux/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/posts/how-to-play/img/play.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Introduction Why would you want to play audio files and music in termux terminal on your phone? Well if nothing else then because is fun&hellip;  There are more ways ( Programs for play music and audio files in termux ). In this article, we will look for one who calls play-audio.
 First as good practice we need to run:
1  pkg update &amp;&amp; pkg upgrade   commands to update and upgrade our repositories.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
